Revenge has never been sweeter.
Thelma is a action, comedy, adventure film directed by Josh Margolin.
When 93-year-old Thelma Post gets duped by a phone scammer pretending to be her grandson, she
sets out on a treacherous quest across the city to reclaim what was taken from her.
Thelma, played by June Squibb.
Daniel, played by Fred Hechinger.
Ben, played by Richard Roundtree.
Gail, played by Parker Posey.
Alan, played by Clark Gregg.
Harvey, played by Malcolm McDowell.
Thelma is a 2024 American comedy-drama film written,
directed, and edited by Josh Margolin.
The film stars June Squibb as a woman who falls victim to a phone scam, and sets out to find the perpetrators
with the help of her grandson (Fred Hechinger) and a friend (Richard Roundtree, in his final role).
Clark Gregg, Parker Posey, and Malcolm McDowell also star.
Thelma premiered at the 2024 Sundance Film Festival on January 18, 2024, and was
released in the United States by Magnolia Pictures on June 21, 2024.
The film received positive reviews and was named one of the top ten
independent films of 2024 by the National Board of Review.
The film explores themes of widow, scam, female
protagonist, los angeles, california, scooter.
The tone is lighthearted.